<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>API on Omniview - The Integration DevOps Environment</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in API on Omniview - The Integration DevOps Environment</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:05:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PluginContext</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/plugin-context/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:12:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/plugin-context/</guid>
      <description>Structure linkEvery time a plugin is called by the IDE (or a by another plugin), a PluginContext is generated and passed throughout, providing access to the core functionality and data of Omniview. The context provides access to various aspects of the request, including the request options, authentication context, resource context, and plugin configuration.&#xA;The PluginContext struct is defined as follows:&#xA;type PluginContext struct { Context context.Context RequestID string RequesterID string RequestOptions *RequestOptions AuthContext *AuthContext ResourceContext *ResourceContext PluginConfig *PluginConfig GlobalConfig *GlobalConfig } Key Default Description Context N/A Standard context for the request, which can be used for cancellation and timeouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Configuration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/global-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:12:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/global-configuration/</guid>
      <description>The following is a reference for the global configuration available to plugins within Omniview. Each section provides a description of the configuration options and their default values.&#xA;The global configuration can also be found on the Settings page by clicking the gear icon in the top right corner of the Omniview interface. The identifiers can be enabled in the UI under the Development section of the configuration area.&#xA;warning Omniview is under heavy active development - as such, the global configuration is subject to frequent breaking changes until the first stable release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plugin Definition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/plugin-definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:12:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/creating-plugins/api/plugin-definition/</guid>
      <description>The following is a reference for the plugin definition file. This file is used to define the plugin&amp;rsquo;s metadata and capabilities.&#xA;warning Omniview is under heavy active development - as such, the plugin definition is subject to frequent breaking changes until the first stable release. Key Type Description </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
